Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Talk to Mental Retardation Conference (Haywood's Conference), George Peabody College (6-12-68) (Box 53, Folder 14.4138)
- The Idea of a College (Box 53, Folder 14.4141)
- "Project Re-ED: New Ways of Helping Emotionally Disturbed Children" (Box 53, Folder 14.4143)
- Errant Thoughts on Ethics and Related Matters (10-6-69) (Box 53, Folder 14.4145)
- "The Snark May Be a Boojum" (Box 53, Folder 14.4146)
- United States Senate Committee on Government Operations Subcommittee on Government Research, Statement by Nicholas Hobbs (6-4-69) (Box 53, Folder 14.4147)
- Some Errant Thoughts on Undergraduate Education (a presentation to the Round Table, 12-4-69) (Box 53, Folder 14.4149)
- Kennedy Center Director's Annual Report, 1969-1970 (2-27-70) (Box 53, Folder 14.4151)
- Outline for Talk to Department of Psychology, Peabody College, Directions Psychology Will Go In (12-15-69) (Box 53, Folder 14.4152)
- Comments to Participants of a State Meeting on Drug Abuse (3-10-70) (Box 53, Folder 14.4153)
- Remarks to the Rotary Club, Nashville (6-17-69) 14.4156 The Teacher-Counselor as Therapist Talk in Montgomery, Alabama (4-9-70) (Reprints) Science and Ethical Behavior (Nicholas Hobbs) (Reprints) The Psychologist as Administrator (Nicholas Hobbs) (Reprints) The Compleat Counselor (Box 53, Folder 14.4154)
- (Reprints) Research in Mental Retardation - Prospects and Strategies (Nicholas Hobbs) (Reprints) Nondirective Group Counseling (Nicholas Hobbs) (Reprints) Counseling (Nicholas Hobbs and Julius Seeman) (Reprints) Guidance and Some Recent Developments in Psychological Theory (Nicholas Hobbs) (Reprints) Psychological Research and Services in an Army Air Forces Convalescent Hospital (Nicholas Hobbs) (Reprints) Sources of Gain in Psychotherapy (Nicholas Hobbs) (Reprints) Strategies in the Development of Clinical Psychology (Box 53)
- (Reprints) A Psychologist in the Peace Corps (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 54)
- (Reprints) Mental Health's Third Revolution (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 54)
- (Reprints) The Community and the Community Mental Health Center (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 54)
- (Reprints) Helping Disturbed Children: Psychological and Ecological Strategies, APA Presidential Address (9-3-66) (Box 54)
- (Reprints) Ethical Issues in Social Sciences: International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (Nicholas Hobbs, 1968) (Box 54)
- (Reprints) Re-Education, Reality, and Community Responsibility in Research Contributions from Psychology to Community Mental Health (Nicholas Hobbs, 1969) (Box 54)
- J. Seeman - Prints and Reprints (Box 54, Folder 15.0)
- Hostility - George Kelly; Ohio State University (Box 54, Folder 15.1)
- The Science of Learning and the Technology of Education Methods (Arthur Melton - University of Michigan) (Box 54, Folder 15.2)
- The Case of George R. Rosalea Schonbar and Paul Eiserer, Columbia University (Box 54, Folder 15.3)
- Couseling Interview with Thomas L. Trait, a Negro Veteran —McKenney (Box 54, Folder 15.4)
- A Descriptive Survey of Peabody Freshman —Stewart (Box 54, Folder 15.5)
- Transference Attitudes in Client-centered Therapy —Schonbar (Box 54, Folder 15.6)
- The Relationship Between the Psychological Investigator and the Public Schools —Castaneda and Fahel; University of Texas (Box 54, Folder 15.7)
- (Reprints) Rue Cromwell, "Training of Psychologists in Mental Retardation" (Box 54, Folder 15.8)
- Prescott: The Child in the Educative Process (Review Reprints) (Box 54, Folder 15.9)
- Training of Statistics in Diplomacy to Maintain Their Integrity —William Freeman (Box 54, Folder 15.10)
- Ethical and Legal Aspects of Survey Research —King and Spector (Box 54, Folder 15.11)
- "The External Sources of Motivation"— John R. Seeley (Box 54, Folder 15.12)
- Report to Executive Committee of APA on Clinical Child Psychology —A. Ross (Box 54, Folder 15.13)
- Bibliography on Psychology of Pregnancy (Box 54, Folder 15.14)
- Etiology of the Schizophrenia of the Psychological Profession —Isidor Chein (New York University) (Box 54, Folder 15.15)
- Kessan, William. "Sucking and Looking: Two Congenitally Organized Patterns of Behavior in the Human Newborn" (Box 54, Folder 15.16)
- Social Competence and Clinical Practice —Thomas Gladwin (Box 54, Folder 15.17)
- Seeley, John. "The Fateful Trumpet" and "Holy Task and Wordly Wardens: Scholars and Trustees in the University" (Box 54, Folder 15.18)
- Wallerstein, Robert. "The Problem of the Assessment of Change in Psychotherapy" (Box 54, Folder 15.19)
- The Reaction to Separation in Infant Monkeys (I. Charles) (Box 54, Folder 15.20)
- An Experimental Preschool Program for Culturally Deprived Children (Gray and Klaus) (Box 54, Folder 15.21)
- The Development of a Method of Appraisal for Assistant Managers (Leonard W. Ferguson) (Box 54, Folder 15.22)
- Dyscultural Anxiety Reaction (Robert L. Leon) (Box 54, Folder 15.23)
- Counseling and the Learning of Integrative Behavior (Edward J. Shoben, Jr.) (Box 54, Folder 15.24)
- From the First to the Second Kinsey Report (Albert Ellis) (Box 54, Folder 15.25)
- Seventeen Years Later: Clinical Psychology (David Shakow) (Box 54, Folder 15.26)
- Origin of the Terms "Mongolism" and "Down's Syndrome" (Amos Christie) (Box 54, Folder 15.27)
- Eros and Knowledge (David Bakan) (Box 54, Folder 15.28)
- Friends World Institute (Morris R. Mitchell) (Box 54, Folder 15.29)
- More Like Men (Mrs. William Gorham) (Box 54, Folder 15.30)
- "Proposed Research to Reduce Racial Aspects of the Environment-Heredity Uncertainty" (W. Shockley) (Box 54, Folder 15.31)
- Reprints of Carl Rogers (Box 54, Folder 15.32)
- Gifted Child Research (M674) (Box 54, Folder 11.0)
- ICSS - Superior Students (Box 54, Folder 11.1)
- A Day School for Retarded Children and Youth (Box 54, Folder 11.2)
- Case Notes (Douglas Vicks) (Box 54, Folder 12.0)
- Case Notes (Charles Haynes) (Box 54, Folder 12.1)
- Case Notes (Mark Carlisle) (Box 54, Folder 12.2)
- Case Notes (Judy Chaffin) (Box 54, Folder 12.3)
- Case Notes (Mark Estrin) (Box 54, Folder 12.4)
- Case Notes (Thomas Buglnig) (Box 54, Folder 12.5)
- Case Notes (Jean von Redlich) (Box 54, Folder 12.6)
- Box Reviews by Nicholas Hobbs (reprints) (Box 55, Folder 14.3)
- Child Development and Language Learning Conference on Role of Foreign Language in American Schools (7-25-53) (Box 55, Folder 19.00)
- The Psychiatric Interview (Box 55, Folder 19.15)
- On Being A Psychologist (Box 55, Folder 14.4)
- Book on Guidance (Box 55, Folder 14.401)
- Some Notions on Guidance (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.402)
- Personality Theory (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.403)
- Personality Theory and Psychotherapy Approaches (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.404)
- Treatment of Patients With Anxiety Reactions Through Psychotherapy (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.405)
- Notes of the Psychology of Reading (Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.406)
- Anxiety and Weil-Being (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.407)
- Notes for Talk on Ethics and Counseling (Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.408)
- The Process and Outcomes of Psychotherapy in the Case of Mrs. Oaks (Box 55, Folder 14.409)
- Client Centered Psychotherapy (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.410)
- Power and the Personal View (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.411)
- Notes on Identification of Gifted Children (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.412)
- Social Forces and Personality Development (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.413)
- Group Centered Psychotherapy (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.414)
- The Place of Psychology in an Ideal University (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.415)
- Gorlow, Hoch and Telschow Book (1-24-52) (Box 55, Folder 14.420)
- Critical Requirements for Leadership Roles (Annual Conference of Texas Personnel and Management) (Box 55, Folder 14.421)
- The Self and the Group (Nicholas Hobbs) With Implications for Group-Centered Therapy (Box 55, Folder 14.422)
- The Compleat Counselor (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.423)
- Psychology in the Southern States (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.424)
- Optimism and Challenge in the Field of Mental Retardation (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.425)
- The Assumed Role of Insight as a Change Agent (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.427)
- Cincinnati Paper (Box 55, Folder 14.428)
- Le Clochard - Etude de Psychologie Sociale (Box 55, Folder 14.429)
- Counseling in Schools (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.430)
- Insight in Short Term Psychotherapy (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.431)
- The Dean of Women and Administrator and Scholar of the Art of Getting Into Trouble (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.432)
- Panel Number One (Box 55, Folder 14.433)
- Notes for Chairman of Round Table on Ethics and Responsibilty (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.434)
- Symposium: "A Report of the Findings of the Southern Regional Education Board, Mental Health Training and Research Project" (Box 55, Folder 14.435)
- Reason, Anxiety, and Well-Being (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.436)
- The Psychologist as Administrator (Box 55, Folder 14.437)
- Psychology and Ethics (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.438)
- The Development of a Code of Ethical Standards for Psychology (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.439)
- Ethical Problems In School Counseling (Box 55, Folder 14.440)
- Motivation to High Achievement (Box 55, Folder 14.442)
- The Image of a Department of Psychology (Box 55, Folder 14.443)
- European Trip - Chapter One (Box 55, Folder 14.444)
- Observations on Gifted Children (Box 55, Folder 14.445)
- Of Mice and Children (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 55, Folder 14.446)
- Science and Ethical Behavior (Box 55, Folder 14.447)
- Research In Mental Retardation: Prospects and Strategies (Box 55, Folder 14.489)
- Psychology, Medicine and Legislation (Box 55, Folder 14.490)
- Psychologists and How They Grow (Box 55, Folder 14.491)
- Manuscript for Behavioral Science Frontiers in Education (Box 56, Folder 14.492)
- Programs for Disturbed and Delinquent Children in France (Box 56, Folder 14.493)
- Counseling and the Individual (Box 56, Folder 14.494)
- Sources of Gain in Psychotherapy: A Pride of Hypotheses (Box 56, Folder 14.495)
- Strategies for the Development of Clinical Psychology, APA, 1962 (St. Louis) (Box 56, Folder 14.496)
- Teaching-Learning Process (Box 56, Folder 14.497)
- Contemporary Psychology (Box 56, Folder 14.498)
- The Process of Re-Education Annual Workshop, Re-ED, SEPA, and CEC (1964) (Box 56, Folder 14.499)
- Ethics in Clinical Psychology (Box 56, Folder 14.4100)
- Board Perspectives of Need and Content of Mental Health Training Programs - Detroit (Region V) (Box 56, Folder 14.4101)
- Speech to New York Society of Clinical Psychologists, Incorporated (5-15-63) (Box 56, Folder 14.41011)
- The Children - Yes (Box 56, Folder 14.4102)
- Let Us Begin (Box 56, Folder 14.4103)
- Mental Health's Third Revolution (Chicago, 1964) (Box 56, Folder 14.4104)
- Foreward: The Retarded Child (Robinson and Robinson) (Box 56, Folder 14.4105)
- Notes for Speech on Mental Retardation (7-64) (Box 56, Folder 14.4106)
- Remedial Reading: A Bibliography for "Teaching the Gifted to Read" (Reading Institute, 1964) (Box 56, Folder 14.4107)
- A Psychologist In the Peace Corps (Box 56, Folder 14.4108)
- Encyclopedia of Social Science Chapter (Box 56, Folder 14.4109)
- Book —Personality, Chapter One (Box 56, Folder 14.4110)
- Conference for Planning Comprehensive Health services (2-18-65) (Box 56, Folder 14.4111)
- Address to Spartanburg Company, MH Association, South Carolina (1-28-65) (Box 56, Folder 14.4112)
- Opening Remarks, Conference on Professional Preparation of Clinical Psychologists (Chicago, 9-65) (Box 56, Folder 14.4113)
- Introduction of Invited Speaker (Seventy-third Annual Convention, APA, 9-65) (Box 56, Folder 14.4114)
- Child Psychology and Development Deviations (talk given at APA, 9-65) (Box 56, Folder 14.4115)
- SREB Talk on Psychology (5-13-65) (Box 56, Folder 14.4117)
- Child Psychology and Developmental Deviations (August, 1965) (Box 56, Folder 19.00)
- The Professor and the Student or the Art of Getting Students Into Trouble, ACE Convention (10-65) (Box 56, Folder 14.4116)
- Introduction of James Hymes (October 28, 1965) (Box 56, Folder 14.4118)
- International Center of Teacher Education (Box 56, Folder 3.33)
- Design for Doctoral Study (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 56, Folder 3.51)
- The Compleat Camper - Checklist (2 folders) (Box 56)
- 1-1 European Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 1)
- 1-2 European Correspondence (miscellaneous) (Box 56, Folder 1)
- (Hobbs, Provost Office Files and VIPPS): (Box 57)
- American Psychological Foundation (Box 57, Folder 6.07)
- American Psychological Association; E and T Board Williamsburg Conference Miscellaneous: Correspondence APA Speech (draft) "Token Rewards May Lead to Token Learning," by Frederic M. Levine and Geraldine Fasnacht "Science and the New Humanism," by Hudson Hoagland (Box 57, Folder 6.03)
- "Ethical Issues in the Conduct of Research in Social Relations" (a copy of a chapter in the third edition, second revision of the text Research Methods in Social Relations, published by Holt, Rinehart, and Winston) (Box 57)
- "Skinner Redux: The Seductive Attempt to Engineer a Better Man," by Willard Gaylin (Box 57)
- "Psychology in Action: The Subject Pool," by David J. King (Box 57)
- "The Ethics of Behavioral Control and a New Mythology," by D.A. Begelman (Box 57)
- "A Comment on the Ethical Issues Involved in West, Gunn, and Chernicky's 'Ubiquitous Watergate: An Attributional Analysis,'" by Stuart W. Cook (Box 57)
- "Comments on Ethical Considerations in 'Self-control Techniques as an Alternative to Pain Medication,'" by Stuart W. Cook (Box 57)
- "The Scientist as Shaman," by Malachi Martin (Box 57)
- "Chapter 43: Col}cluding Comments Concerning Institutional Research and Treatment," from G.L. Paul and R.J. Lentz's Psychological Treatment of Chronically Institutionalized Mental Patients: ! Comparative Study of Milieu Vs. Social-Learning Programs (Box 57)
- "Token and Taboo: Behavior Modification, Token Economics, and the Law," by Gavid B. Wexler (Box 57)
- "The American Psychological Association Code of Ethics for Research Involving Human Participants: An Appraisal," by William T. Blackstone, in The South Journal of Philosophy, volume 13, number 4 (Box 57)
- "Tangible Reinforcers: Bonuses or Bribes?" by K. Daniel O'Leary, Rita W. Poulos, and Vernon T. Devine, in Journal of Consulting and Clinical Psychology, volume 38, number 1 (1972) (Box 57)
- "Arbitrary and Natural Reinforcement," by C.B. Ferster (Box 57)
- "Notes on the Ethics of Behavior Research and Intervention," by Richard B. Stuart (Box 57)
- "Behavior Modification: A Perspective on Critical Issues," by Stephanie B. Stolz, Louis A. Wienckowski, and Bertram S. Brown (Box 57)
- "The Rights of the Subject in Social Research: An Analysis in Terms of Relative Power and Legitimacy," by Herbert C. Kelman (Box 57)
- "National Commission for the Protection of HumanSubjects of Biomedical and Behavioral Research" (Summary Minutes, December 13,1975) (Box 57)
- "Behavior Therapy and Civil Liberties," by Gerald C. Davison and Richard B. Stuart (2 copies) (Box 57)
- (Sprial notebook) Commission on Behavior Modification (November, 1975) (Box 57)
- Tennessee Family Planning Services: Focus for State Initiative, a publication of the Alan Guttmacher Institute (1975) [2 copies] (Box 57)
- Bibliography of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences (1974) The Hastings Center Report (Institute of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences, volume 2, number 2, April, 1972) (Box 57)
- Miscellaneous: "Ethics: Ethical Issues in the Social Sciences," reprinted from International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (2 copies) (Box 57)
- "Ethical Issues and Behavior Control," (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 57)
- The NIH Record (June 29, 1976, volume 28, -- number 13) (Box 57)
- Ethical Principles in the Conduct of Research With Human PartiCipants (1973) (Box 57)
- Soundings: An Interdisciplinary Journal (Winter, 1972, volume 45, number 4) (Box 57)
- U.S.A Supreme Court Case of J.B. O'Connor, M.D. vs. Kenneth Donaldson Index Cards (Box 57)
- The Hastings Center Report, Institute of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences (volume 2, number 5, November, 1972) (Box 57)
- The Hastings Center Report, Institute of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences (volume 2, number 1, January, 1974) (Box 57)
- The Hastings Center Report, Institute of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences (volume 2, number 1, February, 1972) (Box 57)
- Vanderbilt Symposium on B.F. Skinner from The Christian Community (1972) (Box 57)
- Miscellaneous Teacher Evaluation Survey
- Hobbs, Provost Office Files and VIPPS (Box 58)
- Current Projects (Box 58, Folder 11.69)
- Other Projects (Box 58, Folder 11.691)
- HEW Education Programs for Handicapped Children
- A Protection - Advocacy System for Developmentally Disabled Tennesseans, published by Vanderbilt Institute for Public Policy Studies Center for the Study of Families and Children (February, 1977) (Box 58)
- Service Based (Box 58, Folder 11.71)
- Saturday Seminar (Oklahoma City) (Box 58, Folder 11.72)
- Smithsonian Conference (Box 58, Folder 11.73)
- Institute for Children: "Children With Emotional Problems" (Frankfort, Kentucky) (Box 58, Folder 11.15)
- American Association for the Advancement of Science (February 20-25, 1977) (Box 58)
- Bureau of Education for the Handicapped 6.01 APA Correspondence (Box 58)
- Wolfsberg Seminar (2 folders) (Box 58)
- APA Board of Directors Miscellaneous folder (Box 58, Folder 6.02)
- Provost Office Correspondence (Box 59)
- (5) Cassette Tapes (unidentified) (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous Material
- Minutes of Meeting to Consider the Establishment of an International Network of Child Development Research Centers (Unesco Headquarters; Paris, France, July 21, 1976) [multiple copies] (Box 60)
- UNESCO - International Network of Child Development (Box 60)
- NETWORK (Packet of materials) International Network Correspondence (files arranged alphabetically within each year) (Box 60)
- UNESCO - Network (Box 60)
- Network Project (2 large folders of material) (Box 60)
- "Inequalities and Gaps Inside and Outside the Home," by A.A. Al-Koussy (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Reduction of Inequality in Early Childhood: Experience Through Intervention Programmes in Africa," by Professor M.O.A. Durojaiye (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Democratization as a Means to Reducing Inequality in Society," by Professor A. Abuzayd (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Inequality and Cognitive Competence in Children," by J.P. Das (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Utilization of Health Services by Children in Kenya and Some Aspects of Deterant Factors," by Professor N.W. Bwibo (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Some Ways and Means of Upbringing Thai Children to Enjoy More Homelife Equality," by Professor Chancha Suvannathat (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Region and Socialization: Socio-Ecologic Conditions and Inequalities in Human Development," by Dr. T. Kozma (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "The Socio-Political Determinants of Social Stability: The Case of the Arabic-Speaking Magreb," by Professor F. Stambouli (UNESCO). (Box 60)
- "Social Inequality, Its Nature and Dimension With Specific Reference to its Pattern of Manifestation in India and Past and Present," by Professor A.S. Patel (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "The Dynamics of Inequalities," by Professor T. Tomaszewski (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Some Obervations on Family Style and Unequal Opportunities for the Development of Children in the the Gulf States," by Professors M.I. Kazem and L. Melikian (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Cultural Milieu, Family Environment, and Mental Health of the Child," by Professor Wayne Holtzman (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Children of Disadvantaged Families -- Contemporary Studies in Western Europe: The Relevance to Developing Countries," by Michael Manciaux (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Parent Empowerment and Public Policy: New Trends in Reduction of Socio-Economic Inequalities," by Dr. E. Grotherg (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Sociocultural Premises and Child Development," by Professor Rogelio Diaz-Guerrero (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- "Inequalities of Children and Families in Different Cultural Contexts," by Professor Klaus Schneewind (UNESCO) (Box 60)
- Candidates for Henry R. Luce Professorship in Public Policy and the Family (Box 61)
- Aaron, Henry J. (Box 61)
- Bane, Mary Jo (Box 61)
- Benson, Charles s. (Box 61)
- Binstock, Robert H. (Box 61)
- Bishop, John (Box 61)
- Borman, Leonard D. (Box 61)
- Bremner, Robert H. (Box 61)
- Bryant, Keith (Box 61)
- Bullock, Charles s. (Box 61)
- Coombs, Robert H. (Box 61)
- Dennis, Floyd (Box 61)
- Dillon, Wilton S. (Box 61)
- Elder, Glen (Box 61)
- Espenshade, Thomas J. (Box 61)
- Ferguson, LeRoy C. (Box 61)
- Ferritor, Daniel E. (Box 61)
- Feshbach, Norma D. (Box 61)
- Gagnon, John H. (Box 61)
- Gerwirtz, Jacob L. (Box 61)
- Goodwin, Leonard (Box 61)
- Gordon, Robert A. (Box 61)
- Guttentag, Maria (Box 61)
- Hacker, Helen M. (Box 61)
- Hereven, Tamara (Box 61)
- Hendershott, Patrie H. (Box 61)
- Hill, C. Russell (Box 61)
- Howell, Mary C. (Box 61)
- Johnson, Gregg C. (Box 61)
- Johnson, Thomas (Box 61)
- Katz, Arnold (Box 61)
- Katz, Michael (Box 61)
- Kelly, William J. (Box 61)
- Candidates for Henry R. Luce Professorship in Public Policy and the Family (Box 62)
- Kessner, David (Box 62)
- Kraft, Arthur (Box 62)
- Krause, Harry D. (Box 62)
- Ktsanes, Thomas (Box 62)
- Lazerson, Marvin (Box 62)
- Leik, Bob (Box 62)
- Levitin, Teresa (Box 62)
- Levy, Robert (Box 62)
- Meirer, John H. (Box 62)
- Michael, Robert T. (Box 62)
- Moroney, Robert M. (Box 62)
- Murphy, Jerome T. (Box 62)
- Parke, Ross D. (Box 62)
- Penrose, William o. (Box 62)
- Pickett, Robert S. (Box 62)
- Polachek, Solomon W. (Box 62)
- Rist, Ray C. (Box 62)
- Roby, Pam~la (Box 62)
- Rohner, Ronald (Box 62)
- Rosenbaum, James (Box 62)
- Saario, Terry Tinson (Box 62)
- Safilios-Rothachild, Constatina (Box 62)
- Scholl, John D., III (Box 62)
- Sennett, Richard (Box 62)
- Spanier, Graham B. (Box 62)
- Stack, Carol (Box 62)
- Straws, Murray A. (Box 62)
- Tapp, June L. (Box 62)
- Vanderberg, Richard D. (Box 62)
- Vincent, Clark E. (Box 62)
- Weir, Morton Webster (Box 62)
- Wertz, Richard W. (Box 62)
- Willis, Robert J. (Box 62)
- Wiseman, Michael (Box 62)
- Overhead Account; Expenditures (Box 63, Folder 13.251)
- Expenditures (by line-item number) (Box 63, Folder 13.27)
- Inventory of Equipment and Manuals for Equipment (Box 63, Folder 13.29)
- Distribution of Futures and Issues (Box 63, Folder 13.86)
- 3701-3050-739 Publication Costs (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-801 Furniture and Office Equipment (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-623 Consultants (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-345 Research Associates (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-374 Research Assistant (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-380 Office Manager (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-380 Editor (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-458 Editorial Assistant (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-462 Secretary (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-471 Stiff Assistant (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-501 Clerk (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-617 Computer Expense (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-634 Duplicating and Xerox (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-609 Books, Periodicals (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-681 Machine Service Contracts (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-697 Postage (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-691 Office Supplies (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-706 Rent, Equipment (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-794 Travel Expense (1974, 1975, 1976) (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- 3701-3050-794 Travel Expense (1972-1973) (Box 63, Folder 3701)
- Courses, VIPPS (Box 65, Folder 16.12)
- Space (Box 65, Folder 16.13)
- Tennessee Commission for the Humanities (Box 65, Folder 16.14)
- Center for Health Communication Research (Box 65, Folder 16.15)
- American Bar Association (Box 65, Folder 17.80)
- (Black folder) Commission on the Mentally Disabled (Box 65)